The Observer Records UA062
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Observer negatives, 1972 -- 1989; 1980 -- 1989; UA062.004; 2.65 Linear Feet; 13 Digital Object(s)
  - Staff and Faculty, Students (M), 1980 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00086 (Box 9)
    George Mumford: 10/27/82, Izeman; Mulholland, faculty meeting: 4/28/81, K. Edensword; Professor Mulholland: 10/80, CR, Karen Edensword; Caroline Hine, Milburn Winter (A-B); Dean Maxwell (A-B): 10/17/84, Dan Thornton; Professor Mulholland (A-B): 10/17/84, Dan Thornton; Professor Maskelenkos: 4/3/85, Dan Thornton; Dean Milburn (A-C): 8/28/81, KE; David Moffet: 9/5/81, KE; Dean Maxwell (A-B): 3/2/82, Al Levenson; David Moffet: 4/21/82, Amilie Moses; Betty M. Weff (?) (A-C): 4/12/84, Ken McGagh; Manos (A-B): 9/1, R. Lipset; Moffat: 12/9/81, Allen Leverson; Steve Manos, Vice President (financial?) (A-B): 3/17/82, Karen Sotiropoulos; Vincent Murphy: 2/27/81 (?), Denise Leker (?); Maxwell: 9/1/82, Al Levenson; Moffat (A-B): Karen Edensword; Steve Manos (A-B): 2/8/84, Dan Thornton; Unlabeled (A-B); Professor Manz: 2/29/84, Ann Sherpick; Professor Murkowski: 3/3/82, A. Levenson; Librarian Murrey Martin: 10/21/81(?), Allen Levenson; Vincent Murphy (A-B): 2/29/84, Denise Letzer (?); Tom Munane V.P.: 3/81, Karen Edensword; Tom MacGill (?): 10/20, R. Lipset; Nikala Metcalf: 5/5/82, A. Levenson; David Maxwell, Russian Dept: 10/19/81, Karen Edensword; Paula Mors (?); Amilie Moses: 9/20/82, Ann Sherpick; Mr. Maybarth (?), George, Computer Services: Craig Siater
  - Faculty and Staff (M), 1983 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00087 (Box 9)
    Steve Manos: 10/30, Celia Draughln; Jason Goodrick: 3/4/87, David Mofa; Mayor of Somerville (A-B): 1986, Chuck Boatwright; U.P. Finances: 10/23/85, Peter McKinsey; Don Meggerly (A-B): 3/7/83, Ken McGagh; David Moffat: 10/8, Chris Monagle
  - Faculty and Staff, Students (N), 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00088 (Box 9)
    Nelm?: Allen Levenson; Katie Nocan Tufts Christian Fellowship (A-B): Ken McGagh
  - Faculty and Staff (N and O), 1986; UA062.004.009.00089 (Box 9)
    Summer School Director: 11/30, L Wong; Professor Onjin: 1/29/86, Sheryl Kalis; Dean Nelson Gail Hewitt (A-B): 10/2, Stephanie Wolk
  - Staff and Faculty (O), 1981 -- 1985; UA062.004.009.00090 (Box 9)
    Dan Vanjear: 5/26/82, A Levenson; Ortmeyer (A-B): 3/81, Karen Edensword; Mike Obadia (A-B): 4/17/85, Dan Thornton; OONJIN: 3/81, Karen Edensword
  - Staff and Faculty (P), 1980 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00091 (Box 9)
    Martin Puryear Artist of Rejected Sculpture: 5/1986, Puryear; Bernard Picalla Financial Aid: 9/16/81, Peter Jacoby; Dith Prath: 4/7/87, Chuck Boatwright; Salt Treaty Lecture (A-B): 4/10/84, Dan Thornton; Professor Pfaltzgraff (A-B): 10/26/81, Karen Edensword; Bernard Picalla Financial Aid: 9/16/81, Joel Barshak; Press Ethics: 4/14/85, Ken McGagh; Palestinian Panel: 3/6/85, Dan Thornton; Professor Portney: 12/9/82, Ken McGagh; Lou Pritchard (A-B): 2/21/84, E. Pulver; Professor Parkman: 1980, Karen Edensword; John O'Deary and Dean Colcord: 12/4, Chris Monagle; Margerie Pedderson: 3/9/83, Al Levenson
  - Faculty and Staff (R), 1980 -- 1987; UA062.004.009.00092 (Box 9)
    Barbara Rubel: 3/4/87, Jason Goodrick; URI RA Anan R-14; Portraits Dean Reightman 123 Dr. Rizzone Barangos: 10/8, Celia Dranglin?; Reitman: 3/4/86, Stephanie Wolk; Barbara Rubel: 1/29/86, Sheryl Kalis; Barbara Rubel, Dean Knable, Obadia: 9/18, Ejyo; Dean Reitman: 1/28/86, Dean Reitman on Lave: 2/6/86, Chuck Boatwright; Barbara Rubel: 9/26/84, Rich Rodgers; Carla Rizzi, Packard Development: 8/28/81; Dean Roche: 10/28/81, Karen Edensword; Dean Roche: 10/6/81, Karen Edensword; Dean Reitman: 10/84, Dan Thornton; John Roberto the Physical Plant: 10/31/87, Steven Bushell; Dean Reitman; George Rizzoni: 10/30/87, Steve Bushell; Reitman and his women: 10/1/87, Steve Bushell; Carla Ricci: 9/8/82, Ann Sherpick; Peter Ho: 10/80, Russell
  - Faculty and Staff (R), 1982; UA062.004.009.00093 (Box 9)
    Decision Center and Dr. Rubin (A-B): 2/16/82, Al Levenson; Ex-Congresswoman and Dr. Rizzone (A-C): 9/22/82, Mark Izeman
  - Faculty and Staff (S), 1979 -- 1989; UA062.004.009.00094 (Box 9)
    Schulz: ?/23/83, Al Levenson; Jeff Sheehan: 2/3/82, A. Levenson; Jeff Sheean; Safety Office or Officer: 1979 or 80, Dave Slader; Schlessinger: 10/80, Karen Edensword; Brad Seasholes: 1/27/82, A Levenson; Rabbi Summit: 4/83, Rick Lipset; Frederick Shepler: 1980, Karen Edensword; Herbert Spiro: 2/28/84, Dan Thornton; Simchez: 1981, Karen Edensword; Rabbi Jeff Summit (A-B): 9/83, Jon Spielman; Martin Sherwin Teach-in (A-B): 11/11/81, A Balowon; Unlabeled; Dean Sheehan: 11/3/82, Izeman; Dr. Sampson Physiology Dept. (A-C): 4/7/89, Ken McGagh; Dean Solomon (A-C): '80-1981, Karen Edensword; Salacuse: 9/3/86, Steven Bushell; Harriet Spiegel: 1/21/87, Steven Bushell; Seymour Sanchez: 4/7/87, Chuck Boatwright; Sununu: 5/5/82, A. Levenson; Steve Schware: 1/28/86, Ellen Sackelman; Prof. Herwin-History: 10/20/82, Izeman; Professor Swap: 10/14/82, Ken McGagh; Rabbi Summit: 1/28/86, D. Tan; Schlessinger-faculty meeting: 4/28/81, Karen Edensword; MRS Scolla (A-B): 4/17/84, Dan Thornton; Schlesinger: 10/1/81, Allen Levenson; Jeromi Savage: 11/2/83, Mark Florence; Tufts Religious Staff: 11/84, Dan Thornton
  - Faculty and Staff, Speakers (S), 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.009.00095 (Box 9)
    Attorney General William French Smith (A-C): 12/1/83, Ken McGagh; Head of Accounting: 8/10/81, Craig Srater
  - Faculty Staff (T), 1980 -- 1982; UA062.004.009.00096 (Box 9)
    Liz Toupin: 3/3/81, Amy Liss; Ronald Thornton (A-B): 10/6/81, Alma Solonon; Thai Foreign Minister: 1980, Karen Edensword; Trustees and TPAC: 10/31/80; Ted Tye outside: 4/1981, Karen Edensword; Trustees, Graffitti: 2/28/81, Stephen Morisseau; Dean Toupin: (A-B): 2/23/82, Karen Sotiropoulos; Sherman Teischman: 2/5, Stephanie Wolk; Tsongas: 10/14/82, Allen Levenson
  - Faculty Meeting, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.009.00097 (Box 9)
    Faculty Meeting (A-B): 3/26/84, Dan Thornton; Arts/Sciences Faculty Meeting (A-C): 10/12/83, Betsy Rigby; Faculty Meeting: 10/24 or 10/25, Lisa Wong; Faculty Meeting: 3/3/83, Izeman; Faculty Meeting: 10/19/81, Karen Edensword
  - Faculty Meeting, 1983 -- 1986; UA062.004.009.00098 (Box 9)
    Unlabeled (A-B): 2/6/86, Chuck Boatwright; Faculty Meeting 3/11/86: 3/12/86, Ellen Sackelman; Meeting: Celia; Social Policy Meeting (A-B): 12/8/83, Ken McGagh, Meeting (A-B): 10/23/85, Chuck Boatwright
  - Fencing, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00001 (Box 10)
    Fencing (A-C): 3/1/84, Ken McGagh; Fencing (A-B): 3/3/81, Stephen Morriseau
  - Field Hockey, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00002 (Box 10)
    Field Hockey (A-B): 9/21/83, Mark Florence; Kate Donavon (Hockey) (A-B): 9/15/83, Paul Foldi; Field Hockey: 11/21/83, Ken McGagh; Field Hockey: 10/13/83, Ken McGagh; Field Hockey: 9/26/83, Ken McGagh; Field Hockey: 9/18/81, Nick Thomas
  - Field Hockey, 1985; UA062.004.010.00003 (Box 10)
    Women's Field Hockey (A-C): Ken McGagh
  - Football, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00004 (Box 10)
    Football vs. Wesleyan: 10/1/81, Allen Levenson; Vic Gatto (A-B): 4/7/83, Ken McGagh; Football: 9/28, Mark Florence
  - Football, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00005 (Box 10)
    Ellis Oval Field House (A-B): 5/3/83, Ken McGagh; Football: Rob Vohadian?; Homecoming Crowd, Football v. Amherst (A-B): 10/29/81, Al Levenson; [Loose Negatives] (A-B)
  - Football, 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00006 (Box 10)
    Tufts v. Bowden: M. Passalcqua (?); Football and Marching Band: 10/17/83, Ken McGagh; Football (A-C): 11/14/83, Ken McGagh; Football: 10/17/83, Ken McGagh; Football (A-C); Football Homecoming: 11/4/83, Ken McGagh; Football: 9/14/83, Ken McGagh; Football Stance (A-B): 10/20/82, McGagh and Levenson; Ellis Oval (?) (A-B); Football: 1984; Football: 4/16/83, Al Levenson
  - Football, 1985; UA062.004.010.00007 (Box 10)
    Unlabeled (A-B); Football #4: Ken McGagh
  - Fraternity, UA062.004.010.00008 (Box 10)
    A E Pi: 11/16, Mark Florence. No Date Available
  - Fraternity, 1986; UA062.004.010.00009 (Box 10)
    Alpha Sigma Phi: 4/26/86, Sheryl Kalis; Delta Upsilon: 3/5/86, Sheryl Kalis; AETT: Sheryl Kalis
  - Frisbee, 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00010 (Box 10)
    Frisbee, McNoughton and Levine (A-B): 10/17/82, Al Levenson; Frisbee Team: 3/28/84, Dan Thornton
  - (G), 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00011 (Box 10)
    Generations (A-B): 12/7, Wong; J. Thompson, Guidance and Placement: 12/4, Chris Monagle; Genetic Engineering: 3/13/84, Dan Thornton; Grenada Protest: 11/2/83, Ken McGagh
  - Gallery 11, 1982 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00012 (Box 10)
    Gallery 11 Faculty Show: 12/1, Izeman; Gallery 11: 2/24/83, Ken McGagh; Gallery 11: Stephen Morisseau; Art Exhibit (A-B): 9/8/82, Ann Sherpick; Gallery 11 (A-C): 10/6/82, Denise Letzer; Gallery 11 (A-B)
  - Gallery 17, 1986; UA062.004.010.00013 (Box 10)
    Crew Deshoe aka Qu Deshu Literature exhibit at Gallery 17: Chuck Boatwright
  - Gittleman (Sol and Robyn), 1981 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00014 (Box 10)
    Sol Gittleman: 3/25/87, Steven Bushell; Sol Gittleman: 9/11/82, Al Levenson; Gittleman: 9/6/83, Allen Levenson; Sol and Robyn Gittleman: 2/81, Karen Edensword; Sol Gittleman in his new office (A-B): 9/5/81, Karen Edensword; Sol Gittleman: 8/26/82, A. Levenson; Gittleman, Intercultural Center, Professor Stolov: 4/7; Sol Gittleman- Alcohol Awareness (A-C): 4/81; Robyn Gittleman: 9/1/82, A. Levenson; Gittleman: 9/5/82, Al Levenson; Sol Gittleman: 2/6/85, Ken McGagh
  - (H), 1982 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00015 (Box 10)
    Pumpkins Halloween (A-C): 1986; Harvard Square, Hong Kong (A-C): R. Lipset; Hair Cuts: 10/19/83, Ken McGagh; Handicapped: 9/14/83, Ken McGagh; Haircutter: 3/22/82, A. Levenson; Houston Soap Opera TUTV (A-B): Ken McGagh; West Halloween: Oct. 84, Dan Thornton; Hamilton Pool (A-B): 9/14/83, Ken McGagh; Hamilton Pool Renovation (A-C): 8/31/83, Ken McGagh
  - HBO on Campus, 1983; UA062.004.010.00016 (Box 10)
    Hasken Hall:Ken McGagh; HBO at Pub: Ken McGagh; HBO on Campus: Al Lenner
  - Health Services, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.004.010.00017 (Box 10)
    Health Services H-8: 11/19/80, Karen Edensword; Hooper Infirmary: 12/1, Izeman; Health Fair Dr. Rizzo H-8: 2/81, Karen Edensword
  - Hillside/Medford, 1982; UA062.004.010.00018 (Box 10)
    H-7 Hillside, Andrea's Closed Bridge (A-B): Karen Edensword; Hillside Bridge (A-B): 10/82, Ken McGagh
  - Homecoming, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00019 (Box 10)
    Homecoming, Tufts Night at the Circus: 4/8/81(?), Ken McGagh; Homecoming Parade: 10/30/81, Allen Levenson; Homecoming (2): 11/4/83, Ken McGagh; Picnic and Parade, Homecoming (1): 11/4/83, Ken McGagh; Homecoming Halftime (A-C): 11/4/83, Ken McGagh
  - Homecoming, 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00020 (Box 10)
    Homecoming '86: 11/26/86, Chuck Boatwright; Homecoming '87: 11/12/87, Steve Bushell
  - Housing, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00021 (Box 10)
    Jim Murphy, Intern Director of Housing: 8/28/81, Karen Edensword; McCollester House 13 Housing: 3/25/79; Houston: 3/10/82, Jack Ruderman; Latin Way: 2/1/83, Izeman; Off Campus Housing (A-C): 11/83, B. Rigby; Off Campus Houses Near Tufts: 8/11
  - (H and I), 1986; UA062.004.010.00022 (Box 10)
    Ellen's Housemates; Homeless Protest Rally (A-B):Ejyo Kataguri
  - (I), 1980 -- 1988; UA062.004.010.00023 (Box 10)
    Christening of ICC: 5/88; Italian Club: 11/17/82, Mark Izeman; I-2; 9.1: Tim Ireland; Israel's Ambassador: 3/8/84, Ann Sherpick, Ice Cream (A-C): 2/2/83, Al Levenson; Ice Cream: 9/1/82, Al Levenson
  - IDC, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00024 (Box 10)
    Various IDC (A-B): 1981; Leora Cope IDC: 2/2/82, Karen Sotiropoulos; IDC with Leora Cope (A-B): 2/23/82, Karen Sotiropoulos
  - International Week, 1977 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00025 (Box 10)
    Marlin International Night (A-C): 1977?; International Week (A-C): 3/1/84, Ken McGagh; International Week (A-B): 3/1/84, Ken McGagh; International Week: 3/1/84, Ken McGagh
  - (J), 1979 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00026 (Box 10)
    Jewish-Arab (A-B): 11/15, Wong; Jackson Jills: 10/21/82, Al Levenson, Jazz Band (A-B): 10/13/83, Ken McGagh; Jumbo Fever Giant Elephant Football Game (A-B): 10/2/79; Judo-79: 10/1; Jazz Week (A-B): 2/2/84, Ken McGagh; Jazz (A-B): 3/9/83, Al Levenson
  - (J), 1987; UA062.004.010.00027 (Box 10)
    Jackson Jills '87: Ejyo Kataguri
  - (K), 1980 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00028 (Box 10)
    Kennedy Library, Nuke disarmament (A-C): 10/22/81, Karen Edensword; Knights Columbus Building: 4/12/80, A. Levenson
  - Kid's Day, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00029 (Box 10)
    Kid's Day (A-B): 5/3/82, A. Levenson; The Barbeque at Chetwynd: April 1981, Karen Edensword; Kid's Day: 4/12/84, Ken McGagh
  - Kids' Day, 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00030 (Box 10)
    Kids (A-B): 11/12/87, Steve Bushell; Kids Day: 5/86, C. Boatwright; Kids Day: 4/8/86, Ejyo Kataguri
  - Kissinger Protest, 1984; UA062.004.010.00031 (Box 10)
    Kissinger Protest: 4/12/84, Ken McGagh; Kissinger Protest: Dan Thornton, 4/7/84
  - (L), 1982 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00032 (Box 10)
    Jen Rucket LCS: 2/23/83, Al Levenson; L-1; Language Lab: 9/8/82, Al Levenson; Lottery: 3/17/83, Al Levenson; Tufts License Plate: 9/28/83, Ken McGagh; Living Well Fitness: 9/3/86
  - Lacrosse (Men), 1981 -- 1985; UA062.004.010.00033 (Box 10)
    Men's Lax: 1984, Ken McGagh; Men's Lax (A-B): 4/19/84, Ken McGagh; Men's Lax: 4/17/85, Ken McGagh; Men's Lacrosse Training: 3/28/84, Dan Thornton; Men's Lacrosse versus MIT: 4/1/81, Stephen Morrisseau; Men's Lax (A-C): 3/17/83, Al Levenson; Steve Morriseau: Spring 1981 (contact sheet only)
  - Lacrosse (Women), 1980 -- 1985; UA062.004.010.00034 (Box 10)
    Girl's Lacrosse with Trophy: 5/26/82, A. Levenson; Women's Lax: 4/11/85, Ken McGagh; Women's Lacrosse (A-C): 3/1983, Armin Seifart; Men's Lacrosse Practice, Not Useable (A-B): 3/17/82, A. Levenson; Marissa Didio, Coach: 4/13/80, A. Levenson; Women's Lacrosse Training: 3/28/84, Dan Thornton; Women's Lacrosse: 4/7/84, Dan Thornton; Women's Lacrosse: 4/19/84, Ken McGagh
  - Lacrosse, 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00035 (Box 10)
    Women's lacrosse (A-B): 3/26/86, Alison Ferante; Men's lacrosse: 4/9/86, Stephanie Wolk
  - (M), 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00036 (Box 10)
    Miner, Stolen? Buddahs: 10/19/81, Edensword; Muger Hall Study Area: 11/15/82, Ken McGagh; Minstrel Show (A-B): 4/14/83, Ken McGagh; Menchler? Award (A-B): 10/19, Mark Florence; Medford Square (A-B): 9/10/83, Dorothy Lewis; Jim Murphy: 9/10/83, Dorothy Lewis; MSPCA: 10/14/81, Karen Edensword; Tufts Meridian Editors (A-B): 2/24/83, Ken McGagh; Tufts Magazine: 11/31/82, Allen Levenson; McDonalds Deliverers (A-B): 4/4/84, Dan Thornton; Mailroom: 9/1/82, Al Levenson; MFUTERAN?; Misha: Ken McGagh
  - (M), 1985 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00037 (Box 10)
    Miscellaneous '84 #1: 10/1/85; Miscellaneous 2 '84; Tufts PIRG or MASS PIRG (A-B): 9/27/86, Steven Bushell; Misc (A-C): 9/10/87, Steve Bushell; Miscellaneous Junk; Memorial Steps Gate (A-B): 3/26/86, Ellen Sackelman
  - Matriculation, 1982 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00038 (Box 10)
    Matriculation 1: 8/31/83, Ken McGash; Matriculation, 9/1/82, A. Levenson
  - Matriculation, 1987; UA062.004.010.00039 (Box 10)
    Matriculation '87: Steve Bushell
  - Mayer, 1980 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00040 (Box 10)
    Jean Mayer (A-B): 11/10/82, Rick Lipset; Jean Mayer (A-C): 10/25/83, Ken McGagh; Mayer (A-B): 3/81, Karen Edensword; Jean Mayer (A-B): 10/27/81, Karen Edensword; Mayer (A-B): 9/1/82, Al Levenson; Mayer: 3/11/81, Steve Labaton; Mayer's Letter to Moscow: 10/1/82, Al Levenson; Pictures of Mayer (A-B); Fireside Talk: 10/5, Lisa Wong; Mayer Rock; Jean's House: 10/27/80, Allen Levenson; Mayer, Carving, Fence: 5/18; JM's House: 10/21/82(?), Allen Levenson; Jean Mayer: 3/3/8, Allen Levenson; Jean Mayer: 9/30/81, Karen Edensword; Jean Mayer: 1/28/82, Al Leveson; Mayer
  - Jean Mayer, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00041 (Box 10)
    The President Jean Mayer: 10/31/86, Steven Bushell; 1. Jean Mayer 2. Obadia 3. WMFO: 10/1/85; Jean Mayer: 3/12/86; Murray Martin: Fall 1986, Stephanie Wolk; Earl Meehon: 1/23/86, Stephanie Wolkie, Jean Mayer: 12/4, Chris Monagle; Dukakis and Mayer at Nebhe dinner (A-C): 3/9/86, Mike Willner; Jean Mayer: 1/29/86, Sheryl Kalis
  - (N), 1979 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00042 (Box 10)
    Noclids(?) House: 9/8/82, Ann Sherpick; Apple Jam(A-B): 4/21/79; Dean Nelson: 1980, Pete Ho; Nicols House: 9/1, R. Lipset; NY Times Burning: 2/10/82, A. Levenson; Newspapers: 10/5/82, Allen Levenson
  - Nutrition Center, 1982; UA062.004.010.00043 (Box 10)
    Nutrition Meeting: 10/14, Craig Slater; Opening Nutrition: 11/10/1982; Opening of Nutrition Center: 11/10/82, Allen Levenson; Opening Nutrition: 11/10/82, Allen Levenson
  - Observer, 1982 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00044 (Box 10)
    Staff Photo Observer: 4/19/84, Ken McGagh; Observer People: 11/4/83, Ken McGagh; Fun Observer Pictures: 4/3/86; Keryn Columbo, Lorraine Predaum Observer People: 4/12/84, Ken McGagh; Staff Photo: 12/2/82, Al Levenson; Debby and Sarah: 4/6/83, Allen Levenson; Observer Staff Photo fall 1984: 11/22/84, Dan Thornton; Past Observer Editors (A-B): 11/17/82, Al Levenson
  - Observer Staff, 1982 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00045 (Box 10)
    Staff: 10/14, Craig Sraten(?); Staff Photo Spring '82: 5/5/82, A.L. & J.M.; Staff Photo: 5/5/83, Allen Levenson; Staff; '87 Observer Staff (A-B); Fall 86 Observer Staff: 12/3/86, Sheryl Kalis; Observer Staff '86 (A-B): 11/10/86, Chuck Boatwright; Beneton Observer Style: 3/26/86, Chuck Boatwright
  - On the Record, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00046 (Box 10)
    On the Record: 9/29/81, John Katz; OTR?; On File: 10/19/81; OTR (A-B): 2/3/82; OTR (A-C): 12/2/81; OTR: 9/15/81
  - (P), 1981 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00047 (Box 10)
    Puppet Show: 2/7/84, Ken McGagh; Primary Source: 9/8/82, Al Levenson; Pipes (A-B): 3/22/82, Jack Ruderman; Parking: 10/25/83; Paul Foldi; Pick-up Lines Betsy and Scott (A-B): 3/10/82, Allen Levenson; Pinball RC: 9/82; Tufts PIRG: 3/83, Armin Seifart; Pigbook: 9/3/82, Al Levenson; Packard Hall, Donation Drive: 4/22/81, Karen Edensword; Tufts Police: 10/1/87, Steve Bushell; Psyche Exp's?: 10/28/83; Paul Foldi; New Phones: 3/17/82, A. Levenson
  - Peace Festival, 1987; UA062.004.010.00048 (Box 10)
    Peace Festival: Ken McGagh
  - Plays, 1980 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00049 (Box 10)
    Play Starting Here, Starting Now (A-B): 9/8/83?, Ken McGagh; Suddenly Last Summer (A-B): 2/9/84, Ken McGagh; Pippin: 11/4/81, Karen Edensword; Play Ring Round Moon (A-C): 3/9/83, Ken McGagh; Cross-country Coaches (M&F) (A-B): 9/15/83, Paul Foldi; Tempest, Firetrucks at Arena: 12/2/80, Stephen Morisseau; Easy Targets TA Play (A-B): 10/23/85, Chuck Boatwright; Restoration (play): 12/8/83, Ken McGagh; A Doll's House (A-B): 2/26/86, Darren Tan; Matchmaker (A-B): 11/85, Ejyo Kataguri; Unlabeled (A-B): 1/29/86, Chuck Boatwright; Puntila (the play) (A-C): 10/16/87, Ken McGagh
  - PLO at Tufts, 1980; UA062.004.010.00050 (Box 10)
    Hassan Rahman, PLO R-3: Stephen Morisseau
  - Protest, 1980 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00051 (Box 10)
    Racism Meet (A-B): 2/17/87, Charles Boatwright; TPAC Rally: 2/19/80, Steven Bushell; CIA and Protestors (but of course): 10/29/87, Steve Bushell; Apartheid Demonstration (A-B): 9/13/85, Ken McGagh
  - Pub, 1981 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00052 (Box 10)
    The Pub (A-B): 10/27, K. Edensword; Pub: 2/16/82; Jim, Phil, Al, Barb at the Pub (A-B): 4/21/81, Karen Edensword; The Pub (David and Jordan) (A-C): 11/21/81, Karen Edensword; Pub head shots or something (A-C): 10/24/86, Chuck Boatwright
  - (R), 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00053 (Box 10)
    T.E.A.C. Recycling Center (A-B): 10/6/81, Karen Edensword; Roots and Growth: 9/16/81, Peter Jacoby; Russian House: 2/8/83, Mary-Tara Ward; Royal House, John Constantehos? (A-C): 9/18, Mike Adams
  - Raquetball, 1986; UA062.004.010.00054; Bushnell, Steven (Box 10)
    On January 3, 2013, DCA staff added additional negatives taken by Steven Bushnell (accession 2013.061).
  - Religion on Campus, 1984; UA062.004.010.00055 (Box 10)
    Religion on Campus: Ken McGagh
  - Residential Staff, 1983; UA062.004.010.00056 (Box 10)
    Children of RDs: B. Rigby
  - Men's Rugby, 1986 -- 1989; UA062.004.010.00057 (Box 10)
    Women's Rugby (A-B): 1989; Men's Rugby: 4/8/86; Ejyo Kataguri
  - Women's Rugby, 1982 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00058 (Box 10)
    Women's Rugby: Carty; Women's Rugby: 4/8/86, Ejyo Kataguri; Girl's Rugby (A-B): 5/3/82, A. Levenson
  - (S), 1981 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00059 (Box 10)
    Sculpture on Wessely (A-B): 8/31/89, Ken McGagh; Survivors of Logan Crash: 1/27/80, A. Levenson; Shish-ka-Bob's (A-B): 2/28/86, Sheryl Kalis; Switch Board Operations (?): 9/16/81, Joel Barshak; Sigma Epsilon (A-B): 3/4/86, Julia Gordon; Science Museum (A-C): 4/7/87, Steven Bushell; Jeb Scotch Mirror Whiskey: 2/2/82, JB Lyon; Squirrels: 11/8/83, Mark Florence; Sweet Hall: 9/30/87; Salad Bar (A-B): 3/26/86, S Kalis; Spanish House: 2/26, Stephanie Wolk; Sal of Sal's Market, Miles Uhrig: 2/26/86, Stephanie Wolk; Sheet: 1/83, Al Levenson; Sex and Health Center: 2/28/86, Alison Ferante; Branien Smith: 10/13/82, Al Levenson; Saucepan: 2/3/86, Chuck Boatwright; Security: 2/2/83, Al Levenson; Safety Van: 4/4/84, Dan Thornton; Spice B o: 3/3/82, A Levenson; Salad Bar: 3/28/84, Ann Sherpick; Seasonals Andy and Wendy?: 10/20, Karen Edensword; Stores (A-B): 3/9/83, Al Levenson; Physiology Class (A-B): 10/14/82, Ken McGagh; Steel Drum Band (A-C): 9/27/81, Steve Labaton; Single Sex Dorms: 1/26/84, Ken McGagh; Summer (A-B): 11/10/83, Ken McGagh; Sho Demonstration: Steven Bushell; Saint Francis of Assisi (A-B): 10/6/81, Karen Edensword; Tufts Super Heroes (79) (A-C): Marlin; Spyro Lyra at Cohen: 10/29/82, R. Lipset; Scenes from Somerville/Medford; Lecture on Sexism, Miner 21 (A-B): 11/8/83, B. Rigby; Summit Conference, Arena: 10/3/81, Stephen Morisseau; Spirit Talent Show (A-B): 10/20/82, Al Levenson; Society of Creative Anachronism: 5/3/82, A. Levenson; Unlabeled: 2/12/86, Julia Gordan; 60's Lecture After Big Chill (A-B): 2/20/83, Ann Sherpick; Unlabeled; Safety Van: 2/10/87, Steven Bushell; Signs University Ave.: 10/13/82, Al Levenson; Safety Van: 3/9/83, Ken McGagh
  - Sailing, UA062.004.010.00060 (Box 10)
  - Sailing, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00061 (Box 10)
    Sailing: 5/81, Karen Edensword; Sailing: 10/20/82, Ann Sherpick; Tufts Sailing (A-B): 4/82, Jimmy MacMillan
  - Sailing, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00062 (Box 10)
    Unlabeled; Regatta: Mark Leonard
  - Saraband, 1982; UA062.004.010.00063 (Box 10)
    Saraband: Izeman
  - Senate, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00064 (Box 10)
    Senate Pre-Elecetions: 4/28/81; Senate: 9/15/82, Al Levenson; Senate Elections '81-'82: 4/81, Karen Edensword; First Senate Meeting (A-B): 9/11/81, Karen E; Senate: 3/22/82, A Levenson; Senate: Stephen Morisseau; Senate - Kevin Thurm, Swain, Pedro, Glickman 9/80: 3/81, Karen Edensword; Unlabeled; Senate with Rep. (A-C): 3/3/82, Al Levenson; Senate (TCU): 10/7/82, Ken McGagh
  - Senate, 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00065 (Box 10)
    Senate: 9/28/83, Ken McGagh; Senate: 11/10/83, Ken McGagh; Senate: 3/9/83, Al Levenson; Senate, Squash, Swimming: 2/3/84, Bess Bezirgan(?); Senate (A-B): 4/21/83, Ken McGagh; Senate: 5/3/83, Courtney Ward and Ken McGagh; TCU Senate '84: 3/27/85; Senate: 4/12/83, Jon Spielman
  - Senate, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00066 (Box 10)
    Tracy Hahn: 9/10/86, Steve Bushell; Personals (A-C): 1/29/86, Chuck Boatwright; Unlabeled: 4/15/86, Ellen Sackelman; Alex Schwartz: 10/1/86, Steph Wolk; P.J. Simmons: 3/26/86, Ellen Sackelman; P.J. Simmons: 9/10/86, Steven Bushell
  - Senate, 1987 -- 1988; UA062.004.010.00067 (Box 10)
    Senate Meeting (A-B): 9/30/87, Steve Bushell; Racially Geared Senate Meeting: 4/7/87, Chuck Boatwright; Senate Meeting Dealing with Hawaiian Club: 10/28/87, Steve Bushell; Senate (A-B): 10/30/87, Steve Bushell; Senate Meeting: 10/28/87, Steve Bushell